

Erik Gomez Front-end Engineer

e@erikgomez.co | erikgomez.co | linkedin.com/in/erkgmz

SUMMARY

Front-end engineer with 5+ years experience using Javascript and CSS. Use modern web technologies to deliver websites and applications with a focus on User Experience and performance. Well-versed in numerous languages and frameworks with high adaptability to work in any stage of the development life cycle.

EXPERIENCE

Creative Developer | Rubin Postaer & Associates | 5/2018 - present

- · Lead front-end engineer on the Honda Automobiles project
- Write quality, to-spec code in Javascript, React, jQuery, Webpack, SASS, PostCSS
- Build complex features, content models, and perform site optimization
- Collaborate with CRUX, product managers, back-end engineers, content authors, and cross-functional stakeholders

Front-end Developer | AdExchange Group | 6/2017 - 5/2018

- Developed mobile-first and responsive e-commerce and marketing sites for small and medium-sized businesses
- Built custom themes and UX for Shopify websites
- Delivered projects to spec using Javascript, HTML, Liquid, Sass, and NodeJS

Front-end Developer | Freelance | 8/2016 - 6/2017

- Worked with small and medium-sized businesses to scope, design, and create responsive, mobile-first websites and web apps
- Delivered to-spec projects on deadline
- · Created digital user experiences primarily with advanced HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Software Engineer Intern | Razorfish | 6/2016 - 8/2016

- Developed and optimized front-end functionality for the Honda Automobiles project
- Collaborated with UX/UI designers, project managers, and back-end engineers to convert creative comps into functional interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

SKILLS

HTML

CSS SASS

Javascript | jQuery | ES6

React Node Express

Webpack

GraphQL

Responsive Web

Highly Organized

Attention to Detail

Clear communicator

Bilingual

EDUCATION

Full Stack Javascript Immersive General Assembly 3/2016 - 6/2016